vudu.com 2008-12-18

# VUDU - Privacy Policy

VUDU, Inc.

VUDU Privacy Policy  

We take privacy issues seriously and strive to keep your personal information confidential. By ensuring that you are aware of and understand the VUDU Privacy Policy, we can provide you with better service. Please take a moment to read the following policy to learn how we handle your personal information.

Why we collect personal information 

VUDU collects and uses your personal information to give you superior customer service and to provide you with convenient access to our products. We may offer services in the future that require personal information to be stored on our servers and accessible from other platforms and devices — for example, via a website or mobile phone. In addition, we may use your personal information to keep you up-to-date on the latest product announcements, special offers, and other information we think you would like to hear about. We may occasionally include information about products and services from other technology companies that can add value to your VUDU products. From time to time, we may also use your personal information to contact you to participate in a market research survey, so that we can gauge customer satisfaction and develop better products. If you do not want to receive such information from VUDU, send an email to privacy@vudu.com to update your personal contact preferences. VUDU may also occasionally communicate with you regarding important service or software updates.

How we collect personal information 

We collect information about you in several ways. For example, we might ask for your contact information when you make a purchase, correspond with us, participate in an online survey, or ask to be included in an email mailing list. We also may periodically collect usage data from your VUDU box. All information we collect is stored in a secure database. 

When we disclose personal information 

VUDU will not share your personal contact information with any other company for promotional purposes. 

VUDU works with other companies that help us provide products and services to you, and we may provide your personal information to these companies. For example, we give shipping companies this information so they can deliver your products efficiently. The information they receive is for shipping and delivery purposes only, and we require that the companies safeguard your personal information in accordance with VUDU's policies. 

At times, we may be required by law or legal process to disclose your personal information. We may also disclose information about you if we believe that disclosure is necessary for the public interest.

By your use of the VUDU products and services, you acknowledge and agree that we may disclose your relevant account and personal information to law enforcement authorities, government officials, applicable content providers, or any other third parties to enforce and/or verify compliance with applicable agreements, including the Terms of Service governing VUDU products and services, or U.S. State or Federal laws.

How we protect your personal information 

VUDU safeguards the security of the data you send us with physical, electronic, and managerial procedures. We urge you to take every precaution to protect your personal data when you are on the Internet.

To make purchases from VUDU's web site, you must use an SSL-enabled browser. VUDU uses industry-standard Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption on web pages used to complete a purchase. This protects the confidentiality of your personal and credit card information while it is transmitted over the Internet. 

Access to your personal information 

You always have access to the information we have about you. If you would like to review other personal information that VUDU may have about you, email us at privacy@vudu.com. 

Collecting other personal information 

When you browse VUDU's website, you are able to do so anonymously. We do not collect personal information when you browse—not even your email address. Your browser, however, does automatically tell us the type of computer and operating system you are using. 

Like many websites, we monitor and study traffic patterns so we can make the site even better. These processes help us understand which parts of our website are the most popular, where our visitors are going, and how long they spend there.

In some of our email to you, we may use a "click-through URL." When you click one of these URLs, you pass through our web server before arriving at the website that is your destination. We track click-throughs to help us determine your interest in particular topics and to measure the effectiveness of our customer communications. 

Our company-wide commitment to privacy 

To make sure your personal information remains confidential, we communicate these privacy guidelines to every VUDU employee.

VUDU does not knowingly solicit personal information from children or send them requests for personal information. 

VUDU's website contains links to other sites. VUDU does not share your personal information with those websites and is not responsible for their privacy practices. We encourage you to learn about the privacy policies of those companies. 

If we plan to use your personal information differently from that stated at the time of collection, we will try to contact you via email using the most recent information we have. If you have not given us permission to communicate with you, you will not be contacted, nor will we use your personal information in a new manner. 

The VUDU Privacy Policy is subject to change at any time. We encourage you to review the privacy policy regularly for any changes.
